freemake.com 2019-06-17

# Freemake.com privacy policy - Read our privacy statement

## Introduction

We at Freemake are committed to respecting your online privacy and recognize your need for appropriate protection and management of any personally identifiable information ("Personal Information") you share with us. Freemake has established this Online Privacy Policy so that you can understand the care with which we intend to treat your Personal Information. For the purposes of this statement, "Personal Information" means any information that may be used to identify an individual, including, but not limited to, a first and last name, a home or other physical address and an email address or other contact information, whether at work or at home. 

The following discloses our information gathering and dissemination practices for Freemake website www.freemake.com

## Information Collection

Freemake doesn’t collect any kind of personal information when you use our applications. 

We will ask you when we need information that personally identifies you ("Personal Information") or allows us to contact you. Generally this information is requested when you want to provide us with your personal data, to give us the opportunity to get in touch with you. 

If you choose to create an account on Help Desk to contact the Freemake Support Team, you enter your email address, name and surname, password, location. This data is not listed publicly. It is saved within the Help Desk program and is used by the technical support only to get in touch with you.

When you enter a contest or other promotional event, we may ask for information such as your name, address, telephone number and e-mail address so we can administer the contest and notify winners.

We use Google Analytics (https://www.google.com/analytics) to track our website traffic. It is a web analytics service offered by Google that tracks and reports website traffic.

We may use your IP address to help diagnose problems with our server, and to administer our Web site. Your IP address is also used to help identify you and your time spent at our sites, and to gather broad demographic information. This allows us to see which parts of our sites users are visiting. We do not link IP addresses to anything personally identifiable. This means, for instance, that a user's session will be tracked, but the user will remain anonymous. We do not use this information for any other purposes.

When a user submits personal information, it is kept on a private server not accessible from the Internet. This limits the possibility of any malicious use of your information. 

Credit Card Purchase: Freemake doesn't process credit card data itself. All payments are accepted through the payment service providers https://fastspring.com/ and https://www.paypal.com. Information about your credit card is not kept in or recorded by Freemake, it is simply passed through to the credit card company. In this respect, credit card purchase in the internet is like a credit card purchase at any store.

Such information as email address, name and surname, transaction ID, serial number are kept by Freemake or further delivery and/or registration of the product.

## Use of personal information

Freemake software does not intend to transfer Personal Information without your consent to third parties who are not bound to act on Freemake behalf unless such transfer is legally required. Similarly, it is against Freemake policy to sell Personal Information collected online without consent. In short, Freemake does not sell registrant information to lists. In some cases, Freemake may use a visitor's personal information to understand overall patterns for site usage, to contact the user for clarification on inaccurate information, or to follow up on a customer service issue. Personal information may include name, address, telephone number, etc.

## Links to other sites

This site contains links to other sites. Please be aware that Freemake is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such Web Sites as well as any information they might collect, even though our name or logo may appear on those sites. We encourage you to be aware when you leave our site and to read the Privacy Statements of each and every Web site that you visit, as the privacy policy of those sites may differ from ours. Our Privacy Statement applies solely to www.freemake.com

## Third-party ads

We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our Web site. These companies may use aggregated information (not including your name, address, email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, please see: [www.networkadvertising.org](https://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp/)

We may use [third-party advertising companies](https://d1yfi78xmq69ay.cloudfront.net/pp.html) to serve ads when you visit our website.

## About the use of cookies and personal data

This website uses cookies and similar technologies that store information on your PC, mobile phone or tablet. This is usually stored on the devices browser. We use cookies to grant visitors’ access to different functions on our websites, differentiate the users from each other, and analyze our websites performance and to utilize user-adapted interest-based advertising. This relies to some degree on the use of personal identifiable information from our users – as described below – and helps us improve our website and make our digital communication more relevant for our recipients. 

Our visitors can voluntarily choose to accept the use of cookies through the settings on your browser or device. In your browser settings, you can adjust the preferences of which cookies your browser downloads. There, you can also delete all existing cookies that are stored on your browser or device. Please advise that if you block all cookies on your browser or device, this can result in a drop of our (and others) website performance and functions. 

### Purpose of cookies on this website

### Contact – Inquiry of access

### List of cookies and their adjoining third party supplier

## Children's Privacy

Freemake website is not structured to attract children. Accordingly, we do not intend to collect Personal Information from anyone we know to be under 13 years of age.

## Your Consent

By using this Web site, you consent to the terms of our Online Privacy Policy and to Freemake's processing of Personal Information for the purposes given above. Should the Online Privacy Policy change, we intend to take every reasonable step to ensure that these changes are brought to your attention by posting all changes prominently on our web site for a reasonable period of time.

If you have any comments or questions regarding our Online Privacy Policy, please [contact us](mailto:freemake@freemake.com). While we cannot guarantee privacy perfection, we will address any issue to the best of our abilities as soon as possible.
